vdream.com 2011-10-07

# What's Your vDream?

#### Privacy Policy

### **Introduction**

VDream, Inc. ("VDream") cares deeply about your privacy and the protection of your personal information, which is why we have devised this Privacy Policy. This policy statement describes how VDream helps protect your personal information. By using the VDream website, VDream game, or any other VDream interactive media (the "VDream Services"), you consent to the data practices described in this policy statement.

### **Collection of Personal Information**

When you register for the VDream Services, you will be asked to provide certain personal information that will be stored as part of your registration data. The registration data contains various personal information which may include, but not be limited to, the following: (1) e-mail address, (2) first and last name, (3) country or region, (4) state or territory, (5) city, (6) zip code or postal code, (7) street address, (8) time zone, (9) gender, (10) language, (11) birth date and age, and (12) occupation. In addition to the above information, VDream may also collect and store the IP address of your computer or other networking device, which may be needed to operate various features of the VDream Services. We may also collect data pertaining to your online transactions, purchase history, and VDream Services usage patterns. Further, when you register for the VDream Services, you may be asked to create a password for your account. You may also be requested to answer various questions about your consumer preferences or other information. 

### **Use of your Personal Information**

How We Will Not Use Your Personal Information:  
â€¢ Except as stated in the next sentence, VDream will not sell or rent your personal information to third parties. VDream may sell, rent and disclose your personal information to the following third parties: VDream sponsors, advertisers, or merchandise vendors. Please be aware that these third parties may have their own policies governing how they will use and disclose your personal information which may be different from this Privacy Policy.   
â€¢ VDream will not use or share your personal information in a manner that differs from what is described in this Privacy Policy without your prior consent. 

VDream uses your personal information for the operation and maintenance of your VDream account and the VDream Services. For example, we may use your e-mail address to send you a welcome e-mail message when you first register informing you about the service and telling you how to manage your VDream account. You may be required to respond to this e-mail in order to validate that you are the owner of the email address associated with the VDream account. If applicable, failure to respond to the email and verify the address within the time stated in the email will cause the VDream account to become inactive. This process is designed to verify the validity of the email address and to help prevent email addresses from being used without permission in the creation of VDream accounts. 

As part of the VDream Services, we may recommend for your consideration various products and merchandise. Accordingly, we may analyze data pertaining to your online transactions, purchase history, and VDream Site and VDream Services usage patterns so that we can make recommendations suited especially to you. 

We may also send you e-mail about periodic service or recommended security updates or surveys related to the VDream Service. These periodic e-mails are considered essential to the provision of the service you have requested. You cannot unsubscribe from these mailings. You may, however, choose not to participate in the surveys. 

### **General Disclosure of Personal Information**

VDream occasionally hires other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, such as answering customer support inquiries. VDream will only provide these companies with those pieces of your personal information needed to deliver the services, and the companies and their employees are prohibited from using that personal information for any other purpose. 

VDream may share your personal information with third parties in order to fulfill a service or transaction you may have requested. 

VDream may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process served on VDream; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of VDream; or (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of the VDream Service, or the public. 

### **Sharing your Personal Information**

If you choose, you may opt-in to various features which may be available as part of the VDream Services which allow the voluntary sharing of information between you and a group of VDream users designated by you; for example, a "buddy list" or "friends" who are also registered VDream users. 

### **Security and Storage of your Personal Information**

VDream is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We may use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. For example, we store the personal information you provide on computer systems with limited access, which are located in controlled facilities. 

If there is a user password associated with your account, then you must type the correct password to access your information. It is your responsibility to ensure the security of your VDream account password and not to reveal this information to others. 

Personal information collected by VDream may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which VDream or its affiliates, subsidiaries, or agents maintain facilities. By using the VDream Service, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. 

### **Operational Information**

Some "operational" information may be used by VDream in order to operate your account properly and provide the VDream Services. This operational information does not include the personal information that you provide as part of your VDream registration data, but may include, for example, the following: the date on which your registration data was last updated, whether your e-mail address has been verified, whether your account has been deactivated, what browser you are using, the IP address of your computer or other networking device, and other similar types of information. Operational information may be shared with third parties to the extent necessary to provide VDream Services. 

### **Aggregate Information**

We may collect and analyze information about your use of the VDream Services as aggregated with the use of the VDream Services by other users ("Aggregate Information"); for example, results or analysis of polls, overall usage patterns of VDream users, the total number of VDream users, the percentage of VDream users who are female, or in a certain age range, or who live in a particular region, etc., or the percentage of VDream users who are also consumers of various other products and services. The collection and analysis of Aggregate Information is important in the operation and enhancement of the VDream Services and other business purposes. Aggregate Information may be compiled in reports and disclosed, sold, licensed or rented to third parties. However, since Aggregate Information does not include any information which can be used to individually identify you or any other VDream user, it is not possible for the third party recipient of the Aggregate Information to use it to identify or contact you. 

### **Use of Cookies**

A cookie is a very small text file that a Web site saves to your computerâ€™s hard disk to store information that you provide about yourself or to store your preferences. The VDream Services may use cookies when you sign in to or access a VDream Service. The VDream Services store your unique identifier, the time you signed in, and VDream registration data in an encrypted cookie on your hard disk. The cookie allows you to move from page to page at the participating site without having to sign in again on each page. 

The VDream Services may also use cookies to improve the sign in experience. For example, the VDream Services may store your user name in a cookie that will remain on your computer after you sign out. This cookie allows your user name to be entered automatically, so that you will only need to type your password the next time you sign in. 

You may have the ability to accept or decline cookies using the settings on your browser. However, if you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to sign in or use the VDream Services. 

### **Changes to this Privacy Policy**

VDream may occasionally update this Privacy Policy. When we do, VDream will endeavor to provide notice to users in the following ways: (1) VDream will update the "last updated" date at the bottom of the Privacy Policy; (2) VDream will post notice of the change as an announcement on the VDream Site; and (3) VDream may email notice of the change to all registered users. VDream will obtain your consent for any updates to this Privacy Policy that expand the sharing or use of your personal information in ways not disclosed in this Privacy Policy. 

### **Contact Us**

If you have questions regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact VDream Customer Service. 

Last Updated: January 28, 2009
